Toggle navigation [**Kid**Logger](https://kidlogger.net/)

English

Search

Privacy policy
==============

**Privacy Policy**

PLEASE READ CAREFULLY AND LEARN OUR PRIVACY POLICY PROVISIONS STATED BELOW

TESLINE SERVICE S.R.L. - [www.kidlogger.net](https://kidlogger.net/) (hereinafter “Website”) administration respects the rights of the Website users. We are fully aware of the importance of personally identifiable information confidentiality of our Website visitors and users. This page explains what information we collect when You use the Website.

This Privacy policy applies only to the Website and all information collected on the website and through it. It does not apply to any other sites and is not applicable to any third parties’ websites that may contain links to the Website.

The information we obtain on the Website can be used to facilitate Your use of the Website, including but not limited to:

— the Website organization in the most convenient for users way

— the Website history tracking.

The Website collects personally identifiable information voluntarily submitted by You when You visit or log in to the Website. The notion «personally identifiable information» includes the information which determines You as an individual, as, for example Your name and e-mail address. While the Website may be used without the Registration process, You shall register to benefit from the following options – such as keeping your PCs activity journals on the Website.

When KidLogger works, it follows buyer’s instructions, and it collects information about what subordinate to its PC users are doing on the PC or Mobile phone (hereinafter “Activity Journal”).

The Website processes the Activity Journal to provide reports to their buyer so that he can use them legally and at his discretion without violation of third parties’ rights.

The Website keeps the Activity Journal in its original form. There are cases when the Website provides technical protection of Activity Journal by its encryption.

The Website administration doesn’t share Your personally identifiable information and Activity Journal to any third party, in consideration of kid logger product functions and working peculiarities. We never disclose the personally identifiable information provided by You except for the cases stipulated by the law of the Republic of Moldova.

In some cases the Website Administration or the Website itself automatically makes access to the information gathered on the Activity Journal:

* In case of troubleshooting site performance (only if permitted by the owner)
* In case of collection of general and non-personally identifiable information.

In particular, we respect provisions of Law on personal data protection No. 17-XVI/2007 and provisions of the Civil Law of the RM (2002).

You shall realize that share of personally identifiable information while visiting other sites, including those of partner companies even if the website contains a link to the Website or the Website contains a link to these websites are not covered by this document. The Website Administration cannot be held responsible for other websites. The process of collecting and sharing personally identifiable information when visiting these sites is regulated by the document "Personal Data Protection" or any other of this kind, located on the websites of these companies.

This Privacy Policy should be read, interpreted and applied in compliance with the [License Agreement (EULA)](https://kidlogger.net/software-eula.html), and [terms of service.](https://kidlogger.net/terms-of-service.html)

_

If You do not accept this Privacy Policy, You shall refrain from any actions that are not in compliance with Your rights and legal interests, as well as third parties’ rights when using our resource, products or information.

_

Kidlogger

Keep your kid and teenager safe by using the best cell phone monitoring & tracking with KidLogger phone tracker and parental control tools.

Information

* [Parental Time Control  
    for Android](https://kidlogger.net/blog/parental-time-control-for-android.html)

Features

* End-to-end encryption
* Records phone calls
* Messenger chats log
* Track phone location
* Remote control

English

© SafeJKA, KidLogger.net, All rights reserved.  [Privacy Policy](https://kidlogger.net/privacy.html) [Terms of Service](https://kidlogger.net/terms-of-service.html)
